cities2night.com 2012-11-20

# Cities2Night.com | The Global Leader in Events, Happy Hours, Articles, Nightlife and more...

## Privacy Policy

##### Information Collection and Use by cities2night.com

cities2night.com collects user submitted information such as name, email address, and age to authenticate users and to send notifications to those users relating to the cities2night.com service. cities2night.com also collects other profile data including but not limited to: personal interests, gender, age, education and occupation in order to assist users in finding and communicating with each other. cities2night.com also logs non-personally-identifiable information including IP address, profile information, aggregate user data, and browser type, from users and visitors to the site. This data is used to manage the website, track usage and improve the website services. This non-personally-identifiable information may be shared with third-parties to provide more relevant services and advertisements to members. User IP addresses are recorded for security and monitoring purposes. User Profile information including members' pictures and first names are displayed to people in order to facilitate user interaction in the cities2night.com social networking community. Email addresses are used for the purposes of inviting new friends to join Cities2Night, to add users to members' friends' networks, and to send notifications related to the service. With the exception of inviting friends, adding friends, and notifications, a user's email address is not shared or displayed to people within a user's personal network Users within a personal network communicate on cities2night.com with each other through the cities2night.com service, without disclosing their email addresses. Users' full names are never directly revealed to other members. To facilitate searching and finding friends and acquaintances on the service, cities2night.com allows users to search for other members using first and last name and email address. We may also use a user's email address to send updates, a newsletter or news regarding the service. Users may choose not to receive email of this type by changing their "notification" setting to "Do not send me notification emails" in the user "Account Settings". From time to time, cities2night.com or a partner, may sponsor a promotion, sweepstake or contest on cities2night.com. Users may be asked to provide personal information including name, email address or home address or to answer questions in order to participate. We may transfer personal information to certain ad partners that you have explicitly requested to receive information from. It will be clear at the point of collection who is collecting the personal information and whose privacy statement will apply. 

##### Use of Cookies

cities2night.com uses cookies to store visitors' preferences and to record session information, for purposes including ensuring that visitors are not repeatedly offered the same advertisements and to customize newsletter, advertising, and Web page content based on browser type and user profile information. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. You may be able to configure your browser to accept or reject all or some cookies, or notify you when a cookie is set – each browser is different, so check the "Help" menu of your browser to learn how to change your cookie preferences – however, you must enable cookies from cities2night.com in order to use most functions on the site Please note that Cities2Night allows 3rd party advertisers that are presenting advertisements on some of our pages to set and access their cookies on your computer. Advertisers' use of cookies is subject to their own privacy policies, not the Cities2Night Privacy Policy.

##### Links

cities2night.com contains links to sites. cities2night.com is not responsible for the privacy policies and/or practices on other sites. When linking to another site a user should read the privacy policy stated on that site. Our privacy policy only governs information collected on cities2night.com.

##### Correcting/Updating or Removing Information

cities2night.com users may modify or remove any of their personal information at any time by logging into their account and accessing features such as Edit Profile and Account Info.

##### Third Party Advertising

Ads appearing on this Web site may be delivered to users by cities2night.com or one of our Web advertising partners. Our Web advertising partners may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement. In this way, ad servers may compile information about where you, or others who are using your computer, saw their advertisements and determine which ads are clicked on. This information allows an ad network to deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by cities2night.com and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

##### Sharing of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks

As a matter of policy, except where you are expressly informed otherwise, we do not sell, rent, share, trade or give away any of your personal information unless required by law or for the protection of your membership. However, Cities2Night may share profile information and aggregate usage information in a non-personally identifiable manner to advertisers and other third parties in order to present to members more targeted advertising, products and services. In such situations we will never disclose information that will be used to personally identify you.

##### Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our web site so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If we are going to use users' personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time of collection we will notify users via email or by placing a prominent notice on our site.

##### Invite a Friend

If a user elects to use our Invite feature to invite a friend to our site, we ask them for the friend's email address. Cities2Night will automatically send the friend an email inviting them to join the site. Cities2Night stores this email address for the purpose of automatically adding the respondent to the friends list of the user sending the invitation, and also to send reminders of the invitation. Cities2Night does not sell these email addresses or use them to send any other communication besides invitations and invitation reminders. The friend may contact Cities2Night to request the removal of this information from our database.

##### Email Choice/Opt-out

Members who no longer wish to receive updates, notifications, or newsletters may choose not to by changing their email preferences in their user account. All notification emails and cities2night.com newsletters also include options for opting-out of those communications in the future.

##### Chat Rooms, Blogs, and Public Forums

Please keep in mind that whenever you voluntarily disclose personal information online for example on message boards, through e-mail, or in chat areas – that information can be collected and used by others. In short, by posting personal information online that is publicly accessible, you may receive unsolicited messages from other parties in return.

##### Security

cities2night.com member accounts are secured by member-created passwords cities2night.com takes precautions to insure that member account information is kept private. We use reasonable measures to protect member information that is stored within our database, and we restrict access to member information to those employees who need access to perform their job functions, such as our customer service personnel and technical staff. Please note that we cannot guarantee the security of member account information. Unauthorized entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors may compromise the security of member information at any time. For any additional information about the security measures we use on cities2night.com, please contact us at [privacy@cities2night.com](mailto:privacy@cities2night.com)

##### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, please contact us at [privacy@cities2night.com](mailto:privacy@cities2night.com)
